=The Origin of Eternity=
= أصل الخلود =
=Episode 2=
= الحلقة 2 =
I'm still alive.
ما زلت حيا.
Immortal Bai Ze saved me.
أنقذني الخالد باي زي.
Immortal Bai Ze.
الخالد باي زي.
Stop looking. He's not here.
توقف عن النظر.  انه ليس هنا.
Where has he gone?
اين ذهب؟
I don't think I can reveal his whereabouts.
لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع الكشف عن مكان وجوده.
But for the sake of your sincerity,
ولكن من أجل صدقك
I will tell you, then.
سأخبرك إذن.
He went down to the mortal realms for the ordeal.
نزل إلى الممالك من أجل المحنة.
Ordeal?
محنة؟
Does Immortal Bai Ze have to encounter that?
هل يجب على الخالد باي زي مواجهة ذلك؟
He has three love ordeals.
لديه ثلاث محن حب.
That is, separation from his loved one,
أي الانفصال عن أحبائه ،
association with the hated one,
الارتباط مع المكروه ،
and unattainable desires.
ورغبات بعيد المنال.
Siming Deity.
سيمينغ الإله.
I transformed into a fairy after Bai Ze's enlightenment
لقد تحولت إلى جنية بعد تنوير باي زي
and I managed to revive as he saved me from the thunder strikes.
وتمكنت من الإحياء لأنه أنقذني من ضربات الرعد.
Siming Deity, I beg of you.
أتوسل إليك يا Siming God.
Allow me to assist him to overcome the ordeals.
اسمح لي أن أساعده في التغلب على المحن.
That can be arranged.
والتي يمكن ترتيبها.
However, you're an iris
ومع ذلك ، أنت قزحية
with only three flower petals.
مع ثلاث بتلات زهور فقط.
You will lose one in each life.
ستخسر واحدة في كل حياة.
After assisting him for three lives,
بعد مساعدته لثلاث أرواح ،
the petals fall and blend into the earth,
تسقط البتلات وتندمج في الأرض ،
then perish eventually.
ثم يموتون في النهاية.
I'm not afraid of that.
أنا لا أخاف من ذلك.
Since you're committed to this,
بما أنك ملتزم بهذا ،
I shall grant your wish.
سأعطي أمنيتك.
(Three lives of love ordeal)
(ثلاث أرواح من محنة الحب)
(will be by fate.)
(سيكون بالقدر).
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm good.
أنا بخير.
Master.
يتقن.
Linyue, Bai Ze.
Linyue ، باي زي.
Did you get hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
Master, the entire Demonic Sect is eliminated.
سيد ، تم القضاء على الطائفة الشيطانية بأكملها.
Father, Eldest Martial Brother made this happen.
لقد حقق الأب ، الأخ الأكبر في القتال.
You must reward him handsomely.
يجب أن تكافئه بسخاء.
This is not a place to dawdle.
هذا ليس مكانا للتراخي.
Let's leave now.
دعنا نرحل الآن.
This is the sinister ringing of the Soul-Calling Bell.
هذا هو الرنين الشرير لجرس نداء الروح.
Run the inner qi to shield the ringing.
قم بتشغيل qi الداخلية لحماية الرنين.
Don't let it control your mind.
لا تدعها تتحكم في عقلك.
Halt.
وقف.
Bai Ze.
باي زي.
How dare a wimp
كيف يجرؤ واهن
stop the wedding procession of Ghost Bridegroom?
أوقف موكب زفاف العريس الشبح؟
Are you seeking your death wish?
هل تبحث عن رغبتك في الموت؟
I'm Bai Ze of Qingyun Sect.
أنا باي زي من طائفة تشينغيون.
I'm the young master of the prestigious Nangong family,
أنا السيد الشاب لعائلة Nangong المرموقة ،
Nangong Jun.
نانغونغ جون.
Even your sect leader has to get out of the way
حتى زعيم طائفتك يجب أن يبتعد عن الطريق
when he sees me.
عندما يراني.
I heard about the wayward son from the Nangong family.
سمعت عن الابن الضال من عائلة نانغونغ.
To my surprise, you're the puppet of Ghost Bridegroom.
لدهشتي ، أنت دمية العريس الشبح.
Many young ladies have died because of you.
لقد مات العديد من السيدات بسببك.
I bought her
اشتريت لها
and I can decide on her life.
ويمكنني أن أقرر حياتها.
That's none of your business.
ليس من شأنك.
Run now!
اركض الآن!
Don't be afraid, miss.
لا تخافي يا آنسة.
I'm here to save you.
أنا هنا لإنقاذك.
Ghost Bridegroom is here.
العريس الشبح هنا.
Help me!
ساعدني!
Qingyun Sect is a rightful clan that brings evil down
Qingyun Sect هي عشيرة شرعية تسقط الشر
and upholds justice.
ويؤيد العدل.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't leave you behind.
لن أتركك ورائك.
Bai Ze, what should we do now?
باي زي ، ماذا نفعل الآن؟
It's Skeleton Grip.
إنها قبضة الهيكل العظمي.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
Thank you for saving my life, Hero Bai.
شكرا لك على إنقاذ حياتي ، هيرو باي.
I, Qinghuan
أنا ، تشينغوان
have nothing to repay your kindness,
ليس لديك ما يعوض لطفك ،
but myself.
لكن نفسي.
In your dream!
في أحلامك!
No need to do that.
لا حاجة لفعل ذلك.
Helping those in need is the duty of Qingyun Sect.
مساعدة المحتاجين هو واجب طائفة تشينغيون.
Miss, where do you stay?
آنسة ، أين تسكن؟
I will send you home.
سأرسل لك المنزل.
I have no place to go.
ليس لدي مكان أذهب إليه.
Hero Bai, if you were to abandon me here,
Hero Bai ، إذا تركتني هنا ،
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
I will fall prey to Ghost Bridegroom again.
سأقع فريسة العريس الشبح مرة أخرى.
Shame on you!
حرج عليك!
Don't pester him.
لا تضايقه.
Yue, behave yourself.
أنت ، تتصرف بنفسك.
Bai Ze, I...
باي زي ، أنا ...
Immortal Bai Ze.
الخالد باي زي.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
تجول بعيدًا عن الحشد ♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪ كما تنتظر المزيد من الأشياء الرائعة
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
انعكاس غروب الشمس من الماضي
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted in the sea of clouds♪
جرفت آلاف المراكب الشراعية في بحر السحب
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪ ورست على أرصفة مختلفة ♪
♪Only the catkin willow and my graying hair remained♪
فقط صفصاف القطة وشعري الشيب بقي
♪Let's take on♪
♪ لنأخذ
♪Another year♪
♪ سنة أخرى ♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime as I waved aside the night♪
سافرت لوحدي في النهار بينما كنت ألوح جانباً في الليل
♪The tapping rain♪
مطر التنصت ♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
أيقظ الحزن
♪I'm crying out in loneliness amid pandemonium♪
♪ أنا أبكي في عزلة وسط الهرج والمرج
♪I endured countless ordeals from worldly entanglement♪
لقد تحملت محن لا حصر لها من التشابك الدنيوي ♪
♪Knowing how difficult things are for the first time♪
معرفة مدى صعوبة الأمور لأول مرة ♪
♪After you overcome the vicissitudes of life♪
بعد أن تتغلب على تقلبات الحياة
♪Only then do you understand the fickleness of the world♪
"عندها فقط تفهم تقلب العالم"
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪ أردت الاستمتاع بالسنوات لكنها تحولت إلى كارثة بين عشية وضحاها
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪ مع العلم أنني لا أستطيع العودة بالزمن ♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
لن تسكر بالحزن
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
حتى تتورط في الحب ♪